<system>
  <title>
    Akahige
    <!-- What it is called. Short. Easy to remember. Relevant. -->
  </title>
  <acronym-expansion>
    <!-- If it is an acronym, what does it expand to? -->
  </acronym-expansion>
  <slogan>
    To avoid the subject and not face it directly is what I would call
    pessimism."
    <!-- What if any is the slogan? -->
  </slogan>
  <pi>
    <!-- Who is Principle Investigator? -->
  </pi>
  <short-description>
    Shoestring public health
    <!-- "This system is a system that ..."

	 Syntactic  controls: The $title  system is  a (system  for)? "..."
	 Tag line, under 70 characters, do not puncuate end.
	 
	 Semantic controls:  Purpose of  short-description is to  provide a
	 one  line  summary that  gives  some  indication  of the  system's
	 capabilities  for  things  like  apt.   It is  equivalent  to  the
	 short-desc from the Debian control file.

	 QUOTED FROM DEBIAN POLICY

	 3.4.1 The single line synopsis

	 The single line synopsis should be kept brief - certainly under 80
	 characters.

	 Do not include the package  name in the synopsis line. The display
	 software knows how to display this already, and you do not need to
	 state it. Remember  that in many situations the  user may only see
	 the synopsis line - make it  as informative as you can.

	 (Answers question .)
    -->
  </short-description>
  <medium-description>
    Akahige is a free medical assistant and an "AI Physician" to be
    used when a physician is unavailable.  It will contain an expert
    system for diagnosing medical problems.  In this way otherwise
    unavailable medical knowledge may be brought to bear.  It also
    makes use of folk medicinal knowledge.  Together,
    RSR/Gourmet/Akahige provide a robust record mechanism with which
    to determine empirically the effectiveness of various remedies
    (evidence-based medicine?).  The diagnosis system immediately
    wraps into an execution component.  For instance if someone is in
    need of emergency assistance like CPR, Akahige provides
    interactive instruction.  A large set of SOPs and COAs are stored
    and if interested or necessary may be taught to people using
    CLEAR.
    <!-- Similar to extended description for Debian.
	 
	 QUOTED FROM DEBIAN POLICY

	 3.4.2 The extended description

	 Do not try to continue  the single line synopsis into the extended
	 description.  This   will  not   work  correctly  when   the  full
	 description  is  displayed, and  makes  no  sense  where only  the
	 summary (the single line synopsis) is available.

	 The extended description should describe what the package does and
	 how  it relates  to  the rest  of  the system  (in  terms of,  for
	 example, which subsystem it is which part of).

	 The description field  needs to make sense to  anyone, even people
	 who  have  no idea  about  any of  the  things  the package  deals
	 with.[6]
    -->
    <summary>
      <!-- What does the system do? -->
    </summary>
    <relationship>
      <!-- What is the relation to the rest of the FRDCSA? -->
    </relationship>
    <lay-description>
      <!-- Give a non-technical description of what the system does. -->
    </lay-description>
  </medium-description>
  <long-description>
    The  goal  of Akahige  is  a  free  medical assistance.   This  is
    achieved in  the form  of a expert  system for  diagnosing various
    medical ailments, and  prescribing remedies.  Integration with RSR
    helps pin causal factors.

    Akahige is an important factor  and may be a critical component in
    the battle against  major pandemics.  Although this may  be a bold
    statement,  what  is  certain  is that  mankind's  battle  against
    disease is a battle between two forms of life.  The virus utilizes
    its  physical structure  and  mutation in  order  to outsmart  the
    defenses  of mankind.   Mankind,  on the  otherhand, utilizes  his
    conscious  experience of  the  world to  direct solutions.   While
    people  may conceive  of fighting  a disease  as a  labratory job,
    programs that  help people act  in ways that reduce  the potential
    for  spread  are  just  as  important!   If  Akahige  is  able  to
    disseminate  new  data around  the  world's  networks  to all  the
    population, rich or  poor, it will be able  to recognize symptoms,
    suggest courses of action,  etc.  In conjunction with other tools,
    it  can  help  to   increase  the  consciousness  and  situational
    awareness in the battle against disease.
  </long-description>
</system>